Hannah Starcevich

(425) 698-8808 | starcevichh@gmail.com | Seattle, WA 98102 <u>LinkedIn | Github | Portfolio</u>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a previous career as a Project Management Consultant at Microsoft (2.5 years). I am known by clients and peers for my sharp attention to detail, big picture planning skills and motivation to deliver high quality work. Excellent communication and presentation skills developed from consulting diverse audiences, including C-Level Executives, and teaching English throughout Latin America.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap
- GIT. GitHub. Terminal
- JavaScript, jQuery, Node.Js.
- AJAX, APIs, JSON

- React.js, React, React Hooks
- MySQL

Relevant Experience & Projects

In the Moment - Event & Brewery Finder | Full Stack Developer | Deployed Site | Github Link

A web app to search for events in a specific city based on TicketMaster API and discover unique breweries near the venue.

- **Role**: Project manager, JavaScript search engine developer, CSS lead developer. Used JSON / local storage to store API information and dynamically update page elements.
- Utilized: HTML, CSS, Foundation, Javascript, jQuery, Server-side APIs, AJAX, JSON, GitHub, Git

Weather Dashboard | Full Stack Developer | Deployed Link | Github Link

A weather app that will give you the current weather conditions for a specific city.

- Role: Used jQuery AJAX method to make requests to server-side APIs. Created an HTML page and styled with CSS and integrated OpenWeatherMap API and manipulated the DOM using JavaScript leveraging the DOM API.
- Tools Utilized: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, Server-side APIs, AJAX, JSON, GitHub, Git

Live Quiz | Front End Developer | Deployed Site | Github Link

Interactive quiz for users to test their knowledge and compete against peers to earn a high score.

- Role: Created HTML styled with CSS. Dynamic Javascript elements which display each quiz question with response options for the user. Conditionals notify the user if they were correct or not. Time interval is utilized to determine the final score. Scores are added to local storage.
- Utilized: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, JSON, GitHub, Git

Professional Experience

Project Management Consultant – <u>AG Consulting Partners</u>, Bellevue, WA 8/2018 – 10/2021

Led project management for global Enterprise sales strategy teams at Microsoft.

- Accelerated team success as the business manager of the Senior Director of Enterprise Commercial.
- Led all weekly team meetings for 12 senior business executives and drove momentum across global programs.
- Managed logistics, virtual events, training materials and resources for global networks of thousands of Microsoft sellers, including the Enterprise Commercial Leader, Sales Manager, Account Executive, Partner Sellers, etc.
- Led operations and logistics for the Enterprise Commercial quarterly business review cycle for 14 global regions for one fiscal year (FY19 FY20); captured industry insights which informed executive discussions (QBC).

- Created impactful communications on business initiatives (PowerPoint and Email) from C-level executives that were distributed to thousands of Microsoft employees and Partners.
- Synthesized complex data sets to generate advanced PowerBi and Excel reports to inform global strategy with top partner and customer accounts.

Led the end to end project management of the development and launch of the AG Consulting Partners Website.

- Identified the scope of the project and pitched the website map, content and design to the CEO and partners.
- Interviewed and selected website development team and led partnership through three-month design process.
- Orchestrated the company wide photoshoot and selected all media and images for the site.
- Launched site, maintained content updates such as blog articles and regular updates.

Led pro-bono consulting project, website site design and project management of Ben's Fund Non-Profit Website.

- Led six month pro-bono consulting project and managed company wide support of project
- Designed the site mock up and pitched the design and content to the Non-Profit owners and investors

Volunteer & Work Experience in Latin America

NGO Program Ambassador—Days for Girls International, Panajachel, Guatemala	12/2018
Patagonia National Park Expedition Guide— <u>Tierra Patagonia</u> , Torres del Paine, Chile	12/2017 –
4/2018	
English Language Teacher—Beyond English & Independent Contractor, Santiago, Chile	2/2017 – 12/2017

Education

Bachelor of Business Administration

9/2012 - 6/2016

University of Washington Foster School of Business, Seattle, WA

- Certificate of International Business: Spanish Track
- Centro de Idiomas: University of Washington, Spanish Study Abroad Program Leon, Spain

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

Coding Boot Camp, University of Washington Seattle, WA

10/2020 - 3/2021

Recognition

Recognition - Client Feedback: Chief Technology Officer, Microsoft Dev Center, Serbia (MDCS)

"I had the pleasure to work with Hannah while she was a consultant on my team. Hannah met every challenge with a positive, can-do attitude and provided valuable insights to accelerate success. Hannah quickly became a trusted advisor to the team and consistently demonstrated a strong work ethic and dedication to delivering high quality."

Recognition - Client Feedback: Director of Global Sales Enablement at Microsoft

"I have had the pleasure to work with Hannah on many strategic initiatives at Microsoft. Hannah is smart, driven, detail oriented and is experienced at handling uncertainty and ambiguity. She is insatiably curious and asks important questions and ensures all voices are heard. She is excellent at aligning various groups of stakeholders to one vision and key set of goals. Her program management skills, analytical mind and likeable personality make her an incredible asset to any organization."

Recognition - MVP Award for dedication, passion, and hard work: COO of AG Consulting Partners

"Hannah quickly ramped up in a challenging client project supporting several Directors and a Vice President in Microsoft's Enterprise Commercial Strategy team. She swiftly established credibility with her clients and successfully manages multiple workstreams and competing priorities. She has repeatedly received accolades from the client for quality of work, insight, and ability to operate under high-pressure situations."